scalefusion.com 2019-06-26

# Scalefusion Security - User Documentation

## Scalefusion Privacy Policy

Version: 3.0   
Effective Date: 30 March, 2019

* * *

Your privacy is important to us and so is being transparent about the data we collect and how we process them. This policy covers the information that we collect and share with trusted third-parties when you use one of our services or interact with us or browse our websites. In this policy “Scalefusion” (formerly, “MobiLock”, “MobiLock Pro”), “ProMobi”, “we”, “us” or “our” refers to ProMobi Technologies Pvt. Ltd. and any of our corporate business entities or affiliates. 

We consider protecting your personal data to be of paramount importance. We never sell your personal data and we carry out processing of your data in accordance with the **GDPR** (EU General Data Protection Regulation, specifically but not limited to Article 6(a) to 6(f) and Article 28) as well as the Laws of India (together ‘Applicable Law’), where ProMobi Technologies Pvt. Ltd. (the parent company of Scalefusion) is incorporated.

With regards to this Privacy Policy, personal data means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (‘data subject’); an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person (i.e ‘ **Personal Data** ’). 

Scalefusion enables the customers, users, partners and visitors of its site **scalefusion.com** , to have control over their personal data. We also provide control mechanisms that allows Scalefusion customers to have privacy control over their personal data and enable them to exercise their “right to forget”. This privacy policy details the data that we collect when you visit **scalefusion.com** website and also when you become a customer by signing up to use the service.

#### What information we collect about you ?

We collect information about you when you provide it to us by either signing up for our services or directly to us to request for information or express your interest in one of our services by subscribing to our marketing emails.

###### Information that you provide to us

We collect your name, email and phone number when you sign up to use our services or when you use contact form / contact email to request information from us or by filling up contact form to be notified about upcoming features as and when we launch them.

###### Payment Information

When you purchase a Paid subscription plan for one of our services we ask you for billing contact details, including the organization name, address and phone number.

###### Information we collect automatically when you use the Services

We collect information when you browse our websites, when you click on links, time spent on each pages, browser type, operating system or any referrer URLs, we also use your IP address to automatically determine your country and serve you pages in appropriate native languages when possible. Scalefusion and our trusted third-party partners, such as our advertising and analytics partners, use cookies and other tracking mechanisms (i.e web beacons) to provide functionality and recognize you across our sites and services.

#### Trusted Third-party tools we use

###### Intercom

Use of Intercom Services: We use third-party analytics services to help understand your usage of our services. In particular, we provide a limited amount of your information (such as sign-up date and some personal information like your email address) to Intercom, Inc. (“Intercom”) and utilize Intercom to collect data for analytics purposes when you visit our website or use our product. As a data processor acting on our behalf, Intercom analyzes your use of our website and/or product and tracks our relationship by way of cookies and similar technologies so that we can improve our service to you. For more information on Intercom’s use of cookies, please visit <https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#cookie-policy>. We may also use Intercom as a medium for communications, either through email, or through messages within our product(s). As part of our service agreements, Intercom collects publicly available contact and social information related to you, such as your email address, gender, company, job title, photos, website URLs, social network handles and physical addresses, to enhance your user experience. For more information on the privacy practices of Intercom, please visit <https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#privacy>. Intercom’s services are governed by Intercom’s terms of use which can be found at <https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#terms>. If you would like to opt out of having this information collected by or submitted to Intercom, please contact us.

_Intercom’s visitor data is automatically deleted after 9 months if since then you’ve never visited our site again_.

Intercom is committed to and has implemented GDPR compliance in their tools, you can read Intercom’s privacy policy and GDPR commitment below:

  * <https://docs.intercom.com/pricing-privacy-and-terms/data-protection/how-were-preparing-for-gdpr>

###### Hubspot

We use Hubspot as sales CRM to automate our lead generation stuff. You can read about Hubspot privacy policy [here](https://legal.hubspot.com/privacy-policy)

###### Hotjar

We use Hotjar in order to better understand our users’ needs and to optimize this service and experience. Hotjar is a technology service that helps us better understand our users experience (e.g. how much time they spend on which pages, which links they choose to click, what users do and don’t like, etc.) and this enables us to build and maintain our service with user feedback. Hotjar uses cookies and other technologies to collect data on our users’ behavior and their devices (in particular device’s IP address (captured and stored only in anonymized form), device screen size, device type (unique device identifiers), browser information, geographic location (country only), preferred language used to display our website). Hotjar stores this information in a pseudonymized user profile. Neither Hotjar nor we will ever use this information to identify individual users or to match it with further data on an individual user. For further details, please see Hotjar’s privacy policy by clicking on this [link](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacy).

_You can opt-out to the creation of a user profile, Hotjar’s storing of data about your usage of our site and Hotjar’s use of tracking cookies on other websites by following this[opt-out link](https://www.hotjar.com/opt-out)._

###### Autopilot

We use Autopilot for our marketing automation for user onboarding emails which explain to users several useful features about Scalefusion. Autopilot may collect IP address, browser type, domain name, referring URL, page views and information relating to the device through which you access our website. In addition, we collect information such as name, e-mail address and other contact information. Information is stored on Autopilot’s servers. More information about [Autopilot’s privacy policy](https://autopilothq.com/privacypolicy.html).

###### Calendly

We use Calendly to schedule online meetings through our website. If you schedule a meeting on our website, this data is stored in the United States of America. You can read about Calendly privacy policy [here](https://calendly.com/pages/privacy).

###### Amplitude

We use Amplitude for product analytics and usage tracking which allows us to improve our product, functionalities and usability. You can read about Amplitude privacy policy [here](https://amplitude.com/privacy).

###### Clearbit

We use Clearbit for lead enrichment purpose. EU suppression settings are enabled for Clearbit. You can read the privacy policy or claim your data [here](https://clearbit.com/privacy).

#### Sharing and disclosure to Third Parties

We share information we collect with entities or affiliated companies and, in some cases, with prospective affiliates. Affiliated companies are companies owned or operated by us. The protections of this privacy policy apply to the information we share in these circumstances.

**ProMobi Companies** : We share information we have about you with other ProMobi corporate entities or affiliates in order to operate and improve products and services and to offer other ProMobi affiliated services to you. 

**Business Transfers** : We may share or transfer information we collect under this privacy policy in connection with any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on the Services if such a transaction takes place, as well as any choices you may have regarding your information.

**With Your Consent** : Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties.

#### Communication with you

We may occasionally send you emails about product updates, changes in privacy policy, updates in terms of service, to offer customer support and marketing emails. You shall have the ability to unsubscribe or opt-out from some of these emails from your account’s notification settings:

The following email communication types can be opted-out:

  * All types of Marketing emails
  * Updates in Products or new Releases emails

The following are transactional emails that are necessary in order to provide effective service and to fulfill our contract:

  * Updates in Privacy Policy. ( _You need to know about the changes and may be required to give consent if such changes are made in future that impacts your ability to use the service_ )
  * Updates in Terms of Service. ( _Changes in Terms of Service may impact your usage of Scalefusion_ )
  * Payment complete or failure notification. ( _You have the right to receive the invoice or confirmation of your payment_ ), in case of failure our Support team may get in touch with you.
  * Subscription expiry and account health. ( _These two types of emails are necessary for you to effectively use the Service_ )
  * Notification of a data-breach. ( _we’re required by law to inform you about this in case such unfortunate event happens in future_ )

#### Your Data & Rights

You have certain choices available to you when it comes to your information that is stored with us. Below is a summary of those choices, how to exercise them and any limitations.

You have the right to request a copy of your information in electronic format, you can object to our use of your information (including for Marketing purposes), request removal of your account and all associated data. Below we describe the processes and tools which you can use to do so, where your account is managed by your employeer or an Administrator, you may need to contact your administrator to assist you in your request.

Your choices or requests may be limited in cases, for example: if you’ve asked us to delete your information which we or your administrator or your employeer are permitted by law to keep or have compelling legitimate interest to keep. If you’ve asked us to share your data with third-parties for example integrating Scalefusion features with third-party apps or browser extensions, then you’ll need to contact those third-party service providers to delete or restrict your information.

**Access of Information** : Scalefusion lets you access and modify certain information about you, which you can access by logging into the dashboard and your user profile.

**Opt-out of Email Communications** : You may opt-out from receiving promotional email communication from us while signing up or using the ‘unsubscribe’ link from the email. You can also change your notification preferences from your user account notification settings in Scalefusion.

You may be able to opt out of receiving personalized advertisements from other companies who are members of the Network Advertising Initiative or who subscribe to the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising. For more information about this practice and to understand your options, please visit: [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/), <http://optout.networkadvertising.org/> and [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).

**Removal of Your Account** : You can request removal of your account and associated data (excluding the information which we are required and permitted by law to retain), you can login to the Scalefusion dashboard and request deletion of your account from your profile settings. **The invoices or previous payment information will not be removed, as those we need to retain for accounting purpose**.

**Data Portability** : Data portability is the ability to obtain some of your information in a format that you can move from one service provider to another. In the industry where we operate, there is no standard yet for data-portability, hence this applies to some of your information, but not to all of your information. Should you request to receive a copy of your information, we’ll provide you an electronic file that contains your basic account information and the information that you created which are under your sole control (i) Scalefusion Enterprise Store i.e app bundles. (ii) All files in Scalefusion Content Management (iii) All wallpaper images in Scalefusion Branding (iv) All whitelisted/blacklisted websites (v) all location data from all of your devices.

#### Data Security

Visit **Scalefusion Security** and App Permissions page to know more about the permissions and the data that is collected using those permissions.

#### Notice to End Users

Scalefusion and associated products are intended for use by organizations. Where the Services are made available to you through an organization (e.g. your employer), that organization is the administrator of the Services and is responsible for the accounts and/or Service sites over which it has control. If this is the case, please direct your data privacy questions to your administrator, as your use of the Services is subject to that organization’s policies. We are not responsible for the privacy or security practices of an administrator’s organization, which may be different than this policy. 

Administrators are able to:

  * require you to reset your account password;
  * restrict, suspend or terminate your access to the Services;
  * access information in and about your account;
  * access or retain information stored as part of your account;
  * install or uninstall third-party apps or other integrations 

In some cases, administrators can also:

  * restrict, suspend or terminate your account access;
  * change the email address associated with your account;
  * change your information, including profile information;
  * restrict your ability to edit, restrict, modify or delete information

Even if the Services are not currently administered to you by an organization, if you use an email address provided by an organization (such as your work email address) to access the Services, then the owner of the domain associated with your email address (e.g. your employer) may assert administrative control over your account and use of the Services at a later date. You will be notified if this happens. 

If you do not want an administrator to be able to assert control over your account or use of the Services, use your personal email address to register for or access the Services. If an administrator has not already asserted control over your account or access to the Services, you can update the email address associated with your account through your account settings in your profile. Once an administrator asserts control over your account or use of the Services, you will no longer be able to change the email address associated with your account without administrator approval.

Please contact your organization or refer to your administrator’s organizational policies for more information.

#### Policy towards minors or children

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 18 or knowingly allow such persons to register for the Services (as that term is defined in our Terms of Use). No one under age 18 may provide any personal information to us or on the Services. If we become aware that a child under 18 has provided us with personal information, we will take steps to delete such information. If you become aware that a child has provided us with personal information, please contact [Scalefusion support](mailto:support@scalefusion.com).

#### Revisions of this policy

We may revise or change this privacy policy from time to time. We will post any privacy policy changes on our website or by sending you an email notification. We encourage you to review our privacy policy whenever you use our Services to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

If you do not agree with any changes to this privacy policy, you will need to stop using the Services and deactivate your account(s), as outlined above.

#### Contact Details

Your information is controlled by ProMobi Technologies Pvt. Ltd. If you have questions or concerns about how your information is handled, please send your inquiry to ProMobi Technologies Pvt. Ltd.

* * *

ProMobi Technologies Pvt Ltd   
101-B, Gamma 1, Giga Space IT Park,   
Viman Nagar,   
Pune, 411014, Maharashtra, India. 

Phone: +1-650-273-5999
